now that you have completed session
three of unit two it is time to complete
the questions in the assessment booklet
for section three there are two
questions relating to the two learning
outcomes question one is all about
identifying elements that contribute to
good visual management this is broken up
into three parts the very first part
relates to what you need to consider
when preparing to implement visual
management techniques so what questions
do you need to ask the second part is
how can you implement the empties what
do you need to consider when you're
implementing them for them to be
effective and for utilizing PMT's once
they've been implemented how can you
maintain their effectiveness for
question 2 you are asked to prepare
probe with visual indicators for one of
the scenarios below so what you need to
do is look at the three scenarios a B or
C and select one of those when you've
read through the scenario you need to
think about the materials that you could
use as B empties which would be
effective from that using those
materials how could you use them and
what we would use use those materials to
make sure that they were effective as
visual indicators and for the final part
of that you then need to think about why
those tools and visual indicators are
appropriate so why did you select those
you're really just explained in your
justifying your response thank you